[{"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9ec", "answers": [{"answer": "have finished/arrived", "id": "h3t3J", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have been finished/ arrived", "id": "CdnyY", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had been finished/arrived", "id": "eszTw", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had finished/arrived", "id": "0hiEp", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.499Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9ec", "question": "The preparations................by the time the guest..................", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.590Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9ee", "answers": [{"answer": "has been running", "id": "6p896", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "has run", "id": "qChGE", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "be running", "id": "W2Aaj", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "was running", "id": "dDWZo", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.532Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9ee", "question": "He is exhausted. He ............. around the whole afternoon trying  to clean the house before the guests arrive.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.618Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f0", "answers": [{"answer": "came", "id": "hkmrV", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "come", "id": "9atID", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "going to come", "id": "zbYg6", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "are coming", "id": "zKdpt", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.542Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f0", "question": "My sister and her husband .......... over to my house for dinner tomorrow evening.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.626Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f2", "answers": [{"answer": "when he arrived", "id": "F3NTO", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "he had arrived", "id": "6J9JE", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "than he arrived", "id": "dBS7l", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had he arrived", "id": "4aOXg", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.553Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f2", "question": "Hardly ……….. when the argument began.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.633Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f4", "answers": [{"answer": "carry", "id": "nPNAZ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "must carry", "id": "ozHAC", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have been carrying", "id": "snDn0", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "am carrying", "id": "3WJBO", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.563Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f4", "question": "I ........... this letter around for days without looking at it.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.642Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f6", "answers": [{"answer": "will finish", "id": "Kb0yq", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "finished", "id": "Ngswv", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have finished", "id": "uKCrj", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "will have finished", "id": "IEcKo", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.576Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f6", "question": "I would really like to join you on a skiing trip but I can’t do it until I ............. my thesis.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.648Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f8", "answers": [{"answer": "arrives", "id": "SaH3Q", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "is arriving", "id": "dAuZm", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "will be arriving", "id": "6VpMU", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "arrived", "id": "bBs1w", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.583Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9f8", "question": "My boss’s plane...............  at 10:15 tomorrow morning, but I can’t pick him up.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.654Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9fa", "answers": [{"answer": "will have been studying", "id": "mT6ty", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had been studying", "id": "xJGYe", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had been studied", "id": "FyFFa", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "will have studied", "id": "6rbpo", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.592Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9fa", "question": "By the end of last March, I ......... English for 5 years.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.664Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9fc", "answers": [{"answer": "tried", "id": "e7SbA", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "was trying", "id": "thyl0", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "is trying", "id": "QjD6G", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "tries", "id": "b6hiP", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.601Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9fc", "question": "At present, the new director ........... to foster a culture of open cummunication within the company.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.674Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9fe", "answers": [{"answer": "kept", "id": "PWSZ0", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "keeps", "id": "V4BHI", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had kept", "id": "4iXJP", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "is keeping", "id": "vpZAQ", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.612Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2db9fe", "question": "Kì............. trying to pass her driving test but she fails every time.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.681Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba00", "answers": [{"answer": "Have you ever locked", "id": "lBII6", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Do you ever lock", "id": "uSg2T", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Had you ever locked", "id": "dlaNL", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Are you ever locking", "id": "jXwk6", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.621Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba00", "question": "My room-mate yells at my face “............... the doors before you leave the room ?”", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.688Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba02", "answers": [{"answer": "witness", "id": "DPP0Z", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have witnessed", "id": "mnnxk", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "witnessed", "id": "5COCF", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "are witnessing", "id": "XnwUT", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.631Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba02", "question": "For the last 20 years, we ............. significant changes in the world of science and technology.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.698Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba04", "answers": [{"answer": "preserve", "id": "FOxiO", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "because", "id": "xsR0U", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "many lives", "id": "E4d2e", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "were lost", "id": "2RSDI", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.645Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba04", "question": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [{"length": 8, "offset": 20, "style": "UNDERLINE"}, {"length": 7, "offset": 61, "style": "UNDERLINE"}, {"length": 10, "offset": 122, "style": "UNDERLINE"}, {"length": 9, "offset": 133, "style": "UNDERLINE"}], "key": "9il47", "text": "Gettysburg has been preserve as a national historic monument because it was the site of a major Civil War battle in which many lives were lost.", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.705Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba06", "answers": [{"answer": "will go", "id": "tO7rx", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "with", "id": "02WNK", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "as soon as", "id": "BjhXK", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "will finish", "id": "HfJDJ", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.657Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba06", "question": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [{"length": 7, "offset": 2, "style": "UNDERLINE"}, {"length": 4, "offset": 10, "style": "UNDERLINE"}, {"length": 10, "offset": 19, "style": "UNDERLINE"}, {"length": 11, "offset": 32, "style": "UNDERLINE"}], "key": "5615t", "text": "I will go with you as soon as I will finish my homework", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.720Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba08", "answers": [{"answer": "is studying", "id": "U5M6T", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "has been studying", "id": "qXfGu", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "studies", "id": "tsEge", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "studied", "id": "bTCb7", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.664Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba08", "question": "Kì .............. law for 4 years now at Harvard.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.733Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba0a", "answers": [{"answer": "rises", "id": "o1Opr", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "has risen", "id": "DRnDS", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "was rising", "id": "UrsEd", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "rose", "id": "uG3nj", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.672Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba0a", "question": "Our industrial output ............ from 2 billion in 2002 to 4 billion this year.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.741Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba0c", "answers": [{"answer": "have never known", "id": "IL8EL", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have never been knowing", "id": "333AN", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "never know", "id": "sXayf", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "7d9qs", "text": "had never known", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "PvxDx", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.680Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba0c", "question": "It is blowing so hard. We ............. such a terrible storm.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.754Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba0e", "answers": [{"answer": "has been chosen", "id": "qeZM7", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have been choosen", "id": "4w14u", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "were choosing", "id": "A0bZA", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "chosen", "id": "MIN5N", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.686Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba0e", "question": "Only one of our gifted students ............ to participate in the final competition.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.768Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba10", "answers": [{"answer": "was", "id": "vXHaR", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "is", "id": "HrLwN", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "has been", "id": "FC7NJ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had been", "id": "D2OEL", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.696Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba10", "question": "Due to ever more spreading poaching, there .............. a dramatic decline in the number of elephants over the last decade.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.776Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba12", "answers": [{"answer": "will have been staying", "id": "6AeNn", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "will have stayed", "id": "lYexv", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "stay", "id": "tO81b", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "will be staying", "id": "HblIO", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-15T14:46:09.703Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599309314a9c7f202d2dba12", "question": "I .............. with my aunt when I am on holiday in Ho Chi Minh City next month.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-15T14:49:18.784Z"}]